Hello everyone. Welcome to the Plain
Bagel. I'm your host Richard Coffin.
Welcome to the 10th ever Tik Tok React
Plain Bagel video. Uh hard to believe
we've we've done 10 of these, but uh
with us getting the news out of the US
that the country has actually cut a deal
to keep Tik Tok in the country. Sounds
like we're going to be sticking around
with this series uh for for better or
for worse overall. Uh for those new to
the channel, welcome. My name is Richard
Coffin. I'm a registered portfolio
manager, a CFA charter holder, and a CFP
professional. And today I'll be reacting
to some finance Tik Tok, some
#notfinancial advice to give some input,
some feedback, and try to make things
constructive, educational, and to
celebrate this anniversary of sorts. We
have a super sized episode for you
today. So, buckle up. We'll get through
this together. And uh yeah, let's hop
right into it. If I had just $1,000 to
invest in 2025, here's exactly how I
would break it down. This is coming from
a dude that used to live in his parents'
basement to now being worth eight
figures. The first $250 I would put into
QQQ. It's made up of companies like
Nvidia, Microsoft, and Google making up
the Mag 7. Has faster growth, higher
volatility, and averaging around 18%
annually. The next $250 I would put into
VTI. It's a whole US stock market in one
fund like Apple, Tesla, and Costco. It's
super simple, and you're just automating
compounding without hype.
>> So, so just quickly on the ETFs, uh, not
inherently, you know, high-risisk
investments, but I will highlight that
especially when it comes to QQQ, uh,
these aren't as diversified of funds as
they used to be. I think Nvidia, for
example, is like 10% of QQQ now. And
between these two funds, there's also a
lot of overlap. I think roughly half of
the positions by weight are effectively
the same. So, you aren't actually really
diversifying that much by buying these
two different funds. Again, not
inherently bad investments, but you are
making a very active bet on US tech
heavy uh large market cap companies. So,
something to be aware of. Then, I would
put $250 into STRF. It pays consistent
10% dividends with downside protection.
You can reinvest those dividends
automatically for steady income. And
finally, the remaining I would put into
Bitcoin. It's digital gold scarce. It's
global. It's decentralized. And
institutions are recognizing its
unmatched potential. This is the highest
conviction, biggest upside, and
strongest asymmetric bet. You lock it
away, dollar cost average, and let
scarcity drive returns. Make sure you
save this video and come back to it in a
few years to see if I was right. Okay, I
do have some issues with the the Strife
suggestion. So, for those unaware,
Stripe is a preferred share sold by
Strategy, which is the Bitcoin treasury
company that's raising a bunch of
investor money to just buy Bitcoin. So,
they're effectively a leveraged Bitcoin
proxy. And the issue is that these
preferred shares and and the convertible
notes that they're selling, they promise
an interest rate, in this case a 10%
yield, there's no cash flow to pay those
dividends. They're raising money buying
Bitcoin. And then to pay those dividends
that they're promising people, they're
either selling their Bitcoin or raising
more money from other investors to pay
off the earlier investors, which some
people made the comparison to a Ponzi
scheme. Uh yes, it could do fine if
Bitcoin continues to appreciate in
value, but that's a lot of risk. I have
no idea where that downside protection
comment comes from. In fact, with
preferred shares, shareholders take on a
lot of risk because while this
instrument acts like a bond in that it
promises a fixed payment, a there's no
face value or maturity or in this case,
no conversion rate. So there's no date
at which that lent amount is going to be
paid back. And B, because it's
technically not debt, it's classified as
equity. There's no legal obligation to
pay these dividends. strategy. If they
have a hard time, they can just stop
paying these dividends to Strife
shareholders, which will severely impact
the value of the instruments they hold.
So, I would definitely not categorize
this as a safe investment. Also, in
terms of consistent, they've paid two
dividends so far. So, I don't know where
that term's coming from. Maybe he means
consistent as in the payment is fixed,
like they they've promised 10% every
payment. Uh, but yeah, it's uh
definitely a lot of risks with this type
of investment, as you should expect with
something that's paying a 10% yield.
That's not typically sustainable. I'm
going to show you how to make your first
10K as a trader trading option. And no,
you don't need like tens of thousands of
dollars to start doing this. You could
literally do this with a couple hundred
bucks to $1,000. Even better, just
upping the ante with that. You want to
do is go on a charting platform. I like
to use tradingview.com. I think that
one's the best. Then you're going to
head over to the indicators tab and then
you're going to search up the three EMAs
by this author right here. Then you'll
just add the 8,21 and 50 EMAs. Uh so
quickly EMA stands for exponential
moving average. It's just an average of
the last however many days. So you can
have a 100 day EMA for example. Um the
average is a price over that period of
time. It's called moving because every
new day obviously the period is is one
day forward uh both in terms of the
first and the last state of that period.
And then exponential just means that it
puts more weight on the more recent data
points than the older data points. So,
uh, just a quick explanation, the chart
is basically just a an average of sorts
of the prices we're seeing. This is
going to be the 8, 21, and 50 EMAs. So,
whenever stocks are above the moving
averages, like so, we are clearly in an
uptrend and we're probably going to
continue up. So, this is when you want
to be looking to buy calls. Whenever the
markets are below the moving averages,
like so, you're clearly in a downtrend
and you're likely to continue to see new
lows. So, you can either stay out of the
market or you could buy puts and trade
things to the downside. So, what I'm
looking for is a level that price has
rejected multiple times. Basically, a
resistance level. So, right here, you
can see the stock rejected, rejected,
rejected, and rejected. So, we know that
if it gets above, it's probably going to
make a big move up and you can target
some of these highs for a continuation
move. So, for time, I'm going to stop it
there. Uh, he does keep going. He
explains that later in the video, you
also want volume, meaning that there's a
lot of trading activity uh to kind of
confirm the trends you're analyzing. And
the appeal of these types of systems and
the like is that they seem very simple
and they give you a very clear yes or
no. Right? What's funny is that in this
video you can see examples of where this
strategy would have gone horribly wrong.
Like you have here for example where the
price is clearly above the uh moving
average lines and yet the stock plummets
thereafter. Meaning that you would lose
a bunch of money if you had bought here.
You'd basically be buying at the top if
you're day trading. And then here you
have the exact opposite where the price
is below these moving averages and then
surges right after. So, you have to be
careful with these types of videos,
right? Because anyone can take any
trading pattern and make it look
attractive uh in post, right? When you
have the ability to go look historically
for a segment of time that fits your
narrative or fits your trading pattern
in terms of making $10,000 from a few
hundred or a few thousand with options.
Yes, they do introduce leverage uh which
means that they sort of amplify the
returns you can experience from a a
standard stock by using options for that
same company. Uh but you have to keep in
mind that leverage also expands your
downside, right? The chance of going to
zero is much much much higher with call
options and put options than it is with
buying the actual underlying stock. And
if you're betting everything to try and
see this massive surge in return, uh
it's very easy to to very quickly lose
everything. Now, if you're someone who's
interested in day trading and trying to
see those massive upswings in value,
have no fear. I won't leave you
empty-handed. I'll share a proprietary
plain bagel trading strategy that's just
as likely to take you from a few hundred
dollars to tens of thousands. So,
basically what we're going to do here is
we're going to take all of our money and
always put it all on black. We can
ignore all the numbers here. Uh just
focusing on the color strategy, picking
the one
next Tik Tok. A quick note that Richard
is not actually gambling real money here
and does not seriously endorse gambling.
We hope that's obvious, but because
Richard doesn't trust any of you, he
felt the need to clarify. Anyway, sorry
for interrupting. Back to the video.
>> Today, I decided I'm going to be cashing
out my entire retirement.
I recently discovered, which I should
have researched earlier, that my
retirement is doing really well because
16% of my mutual funds are invested in
Black Rockck and it doesn't sit well
with me. Today, I'll be calling my
financial advisor
and I'm interested to know if anyone
else has uh personally divested. How can
I expect organizations to divest if I
myself
have mutual funds that are doing well
because of Black Rockck, which is known
to be harming communities. So
yeah, I just felt called to share that.
And um if you're my family and you're
seeing this, it's going to be fine. Uh,
I got to be careful with this because I
don't want to be labeled a Black Rock
sympathizing globalist co-conspirator,
but for the thousandth time, it's not
Black Rockck that's buying single family
properties in the United States, which
is what I'm guessing she's talking about
when she says harming communities. Maybe
there's something else that I'm ignorant
to, but their primary business is
setting up funds that invest in publicly
traded stocks. There are companies out
there that are buying single family
homes. for example, Black Stone, uh,
which is where a lot of people make that
mistake because the names are very
similar, but they overall represent a
small fraction of buying activity. So,
you can still criticize the practice.
I'm not here to defend that, but Black
Rockck's the wrong company. They do buy
multi-tenant properties like apartment
buildings and and purpose-built
communities, but not individual houses.
In terms of uh pulling her money out, I
don't know if she means she's 16%
invested in Black Rockck funds or or
Black Rockck specifically, like the
actual company since they're publicly
traded stock. Um, and I'm Canadian, so I
the rules are slightly different here.
But I am aware that with the 401k, uh,
while the options can be limited, there
are typically other funds you can look
into. So certainly a route worth
exploring before pulling money out. And
if you do withdraw that amount before a
certain age, I think it's around 60 in
the United States, there's actually a
10% penalty on whatever you withdraw in
addition to income taxes. There are some
exceptions where you can avoid that
penalty, uh, such as in uh, periods of
financial hardship. There are also
conditions where you can roll a 401k
into a different type of account without
a tax consequence. So, lots of other
stuff to look into. But generally
speaking, the benefit of the 401k is tax
deferral, meaning that's best to leave
the money in the account, let it grow
tax deferred until you reach retirement
when you can pull it out at a lower
income tax bracket than you would be if
you pulled it out earlier, say in your
30s. So, at least she's going to talk to
her adviser. Hopefully, they can share
that information. But just some stuff to
be aware of.
>> So, how long will it take me to replace
my income via the stock market? I had
this crazy idea while on maternity leave
to take one week of my leave benefit,
invested in the stock market, and use
that to sell covered calls to try to
replace my income. I just jumped in
without doing any math.
But now that we're a month in, I've had
some time to crunch the numbers and see
how long it's going to take to actually
generate enough money in premiums to
replace my income. So, the amount that I
started with was $1,542,
which is the maximum benefit in the
state of Washington for paid family
leave. So far, I've been able to earn
about a 10% return on that initial
capital, but it's unrealistic to think
that that amount would continue
consistently week after week.
>> Okay. So, she made what was it? $150
roughly. So,
I mean, we're we're a bit off, but she
she's grounding her expectations. So,
I'm I'm going to give her a chance.
That's good. I'm glad that we're seeing
that.
>> So, I looked at a couple scenarios with
different amounts of returns each week,
and it
>> the fastest that I could.
>> She's talking about weekly returns.
Oh, no.
10%. Okay, guys. Unrealistic. Come on.
We We can't earn 10% a week. 8%.
Now we're talking.
Oh, I had such high hopes for this one.
potentially replace my income would be
31 weeks
and a middle amount would be about a
year.
>> Jesus annualized 5% a week is still like
over a,000% a year. Okay, I'm sorry. You
can't retire off $1,500.
I'm sorry to be the bearer of bad news.
I I know we were hoping for something
different, but like these are crazy
figures. I I know it's covered calls,
guys, but
I I'm crashing out on the fourth video.
I don't know if this I don't know if
this extended video was a good idea.
>> Basically, what I need to do is grow
that $1,500 that I started with to
somewhere between 20 and $30,000 in
order to have enough capital to invest
to earn about $1,500 a week selling
covered calls. So, while this is
definitely a slow process, it will
generate income much faster than just
investing in dividend stocks or just
investing in the overall stock market in
general.
>> Man, there is a lot of hype and
excitement around covered call type
strategies. Uh, which for the
uninitiated, a covered call is when you
own a stock and then you sell call
options for that stock. meaning that you
sell the right to someone else so that
they can buy your stock at a
predetermined price if it increases in
value. And people like it because it
feels like it's generating free money.
You have a stock and while you own that
stock, you're selling this contract,
this right to buy it. And so long as the
stock price doesn't increase in value,
you get to keep that premium that you're
earning, right? Sounds like a a great
deal.
People don't understand the risk return
trade-off you're accepting for that
contract. What you're doing is you're
cutting off your upside because the
stock surges in value. You have to sell
it to someone for less than that value,
right? You you cap your upside and you
only slightly compensate your downside
with this premium whenever you do this
trade. The idea of taking $1,500 to tens
of thousands of dollars should be a red
flag to anyone. It doesn't matter what
the trading strategy is, right? You have
to realize that whenever you're taking a
strategy, someone's taking the other
side of that arrangement
and they're possibly doing more math
than you are, right? In fact, there's a
video posted by Ben Felix not that long
ago that showed for broad-based ETFs
that are covered calls, they over the
long-term have underperformed their
non-covered call equivalents uh when put
side by side. And the problem is that
people look at the yield and they're
like, "Wow, look at how much money I'm
earning as income without recognizing
how much they might be losing on the
price side." In fact, we've seen funds
get in trouble for just highlighting the
yield while ignoring the fact that their
ETF is falling in price. Covered calls a
little controversial. Some people love
them. Most people misunderstand how they
work. And you should not buy these types
of products if you don't understand how
they work. So, I'll leave some resources
you can click in the link in the
description. Sorry if you want to check
those out. But anyway, next Tik Tok.
>> You are crazy if you think that the way
you are going to get rich is from making
the money that you have right now and
just investing it in the stock market.
That's insane. Why? Because what you are
actually doing is you're just letting
other people get rich. Who gets really
rich? The asset managers who manage your
money, the banks that hold your capital,
why do they get rich instead of you?
Because what do they do? They take your
money and they do something with it
proactively. So they take your money and
they take real risk with it. And I think
unless you take risk with your money,
but also with yourself, you're never
going to get wealthy. And so you and I
could go very viral on the internet
every single day if we talked about how
to invest your first $10,000 to get to
$100,000. You could make you could get a
lot of views on that. Except it's
totally pointless. And if what we really
want to do is elevate people to real
wealth where they they have enough money
for all the things that they want in
life, it's not done through investing.
It is done through earning. That is the
only way you make real money. Once you
make real money, you can make more of it
through investing. But in the beginning,
you got to earn. That's it.
>> Uh some misconceptions here. one, when
it comes to asset managers, it's kind of
the opposite. They don't actually take
that much risk. There are funds where
there will be like co-investment and the
like. Um, but when you invest through
BlackRock or these funds, they make
their money by charging a fee for
facilitating that investment, but they
don't inherently have any of their own
money at risk. It's actually something I
find kind of frustrating with the whole
Bitcoin conversation when people will
say, "Look, the the institutions are
coming. Black Rockck must believe in
Bitcoin because look at how much money
how much Bitcoin they're buying for
their funds." It's like they don't
really care, you know? Well, they they
want more investors to buy it because uh
then they'll have a larger base to
charge that fee against, but they don't
really lose anything if that investment
crashes or loses value. So, so they're a
bit agnostic. They just want people to
buy their different funds and be the one
to offer all the types of funds so that
they have the biggest net to catch
investors in. Secondly, when it comes to
their earnings versus investing, I can
kind of agree with that. Um, in that
most people should focus more of their
efforts on increasing their earnings,
uh, you know, improving their skills and
things like that versus trying to
improve their investment returns, you
know, spending more time trading and the
like, because there's there's much more,
uh, marginal benefit over here. But
investing very clearly helps, right? If
you put away $500 a month for 40 years,
even if you earn just a 6% return,
you'll end up with nearly a million
dollars despite having only saved about
a quarter of that amount through your
earned money. Right? So, investing over
a long period of time can still carry
the majority of your net worth by
retirement. I can agree that you
shouldn't expect investing to make up
for a lack of earnings or things like
that, especially because that's when you
get really dangerous with things like
chasing returns and these day trading
kind of high-risisk strategies. But
yeah, just some things to clear up there
in terms of the overall message.
>> When I sat down for the first time to
learn how to trade, the first thing that
my uncle said was everything I'm getting
ready to teach you is all you need to
know. And he told me that the ones that
knew the least amount about trading that
knew nothing prior were the most
successful when it came to trading.
>> How convenient.
How convenient that the people who have
no prior experience who who might be
starting from scratch are going to be
the most successful. It'd be a shame if
if uh you were just selling a course to
beginners to try and Oh, there it is.
Yeah. Okay. We have trader in 30 days
challenge. Easy. And you know what?
You'll be the most successful if uh you
don't know what you're doing.
>> People that already have previous
knowledge, they develop biases when it
comes to trading. They look for other
things to incorporate. They have old
habits. He said the ones that started
fresh and took everything he said for
face value were the most successful. So
when he told that to me, I did exactly
that. Everything he taught me is exactly
what I've been using for the past 9
years. That's wild to stick to something
and believe it fully for 9 years. You
don't get to see any of the benefits of
it the first few years because you've
still got to master psychology. You
still got to master the strategy itself
and the instruments that you're trading.
But then to see the benefits that you
reap, it's incredible. And I hope that
you guys can understand that and try to
experience the same thing for yourself.
So don't forget to hit that follow
button for more trading tips.
>> You know what? I actually couldn't agree
more. Sometimes the best returns come
from sticking to the strategies that are
simple that you know the best.
Damn it. What I find frustrating about
people who promote day trading courses
is one, it's all pseudocience. like
these people are just trademarking
random patterns and indicators and then
using cherrypicked stock prices and and
past performance to to prove that they
work. But also like that focus on
psychology. It's like it's on one hand
it's marketed as something that's so
simple anyone can do it. If you don't
know anything beforehand, this is still
a winning ticket to to beat the markets.
But also it's such a handy out when
people don't do well. Like investor
psychology is a thing that we have
evidence of impacting long-term
performance. But when you're selling
some sort of easy to follow formula for
making money, you can't also play the
card that emotions will somehow dictate
your outcome. It's become a habit that
the first thing I do whenever I see a
Tik Tok now is is check the person's
profile to see if they sell a course or
some sort of service because it helps
frame everything nicely. And I'd
actually I' I'd recommend that for
anyone who's looking at Tik Tok for
advice and the like is, you know, look
at the person's incentives, see what
motivates them to tell you the messaging
that they're sharing in the video.
Because, as Charlie Munger once famously
put it, "Show me the incentives and I'll
show you the outcome."
>> You are an idiot if you're not watching
these three stocks for Thursday's
trading day. Finally, IPOs are back on
fire with this new IPO today exploding
over 60% into the close. And it looks
like it's ready to squeeze much, much
higher.
>> It's funny, there used to be five best
stocks to buy in 2025 or this year. Then
it was five best stocks to buy in this
month. Now we're talking weekdays. The
three best stocks to buy Thursday,
October 2025. First up on the list is
the stock that exploded over 100% today
in after hours on CIGL. This is an
explosive looking continuation style
setup, but it has to get broken out over
this level first. What I want to see
here on CIGL tomorrow is a strong break
over this 540 level over the previous
high of day. If we see that past tie get
breaking in a strong way, I then want to
see price pull back and retest somewhere
over five bucks a share and put in place
a bottom. If we see price put in place a
bottom over $5 after getting breaking
out, we have range to the upside here
all the way to $7.50 to the upside,
giving us tremendous amount of range.
But as always, no break, no trade.
Number two looks even better, and it's
the massive explosion today on Quantum
News on RVSN. Now, this thing looks so
>> Okay, look, I get the boxes. I I get
we're drawing off of tops and bottoms of
candles, whatever.
What are these price projections?
Why are we doubling our our money
randomly? Is it just because the stock
did really well the previous day? Is is
that why we're we're forecasting like
this? Is this what every weekday video
is forecasting? Like that's that's
crazy. Yeah. Okay. So, not none of the
stocks got even close to to what he was
projecting. But hey, it's one hell of an
arrow he drew on there. I was half
convinced just by the audacity. You have
to be careful about these type of micro
cap or or even nano cap stocks. Even
sometimes these videos and and these
types of traders can influence the stock
price of this very low volume trading
stock with these types of videos. So u
I'm not accusing this guy of doing
anything. I don't know who this guy is,
but you know when you talk about these
areas, you can move the price with this
type of influence if you have enough of
a following and you if you have Discord
groups and the like. So, you have to be
careful uh because at times you could
very well be the exit strategy for for
some of these traders, right?
>> I know America is $1 trillion in debt,
but I know how we could solve this. Let
me take the debt, bro. Someone has to do
it. Someone has to step up and be a
freaking trillion dollars in debt. And
I'm not afraid to be that guy. Oh,
>> man. Taking one for the team.
>> You know what I'm saying? Who's it even
in debt to? Who's the one that's gonna
pay this debt? this debt doesn't even
really exist. Let me be the one to have
this debt, bro. Because then I could say
I'm a trillion dollars in debt. I'm a
trillionaire. You know what I'm saying?
That would make me a real trillionaire.
I mean I I mean according to some
influencers. Yeah. You just buy some
properties while you're at it. On a on a
serious note, funny TikTok, on a serious
note, uh that question does actually
circulate a lot. People wonder like who
the hell is all this money to? Um the
answer is actually most of the US
government's debt is to US citizens
because yes we talk about the US being
in debt but again there's different
parties right there's the government
there's private corporations private
investors um and the US government sells
a lot of its bonds its debt to
individuals to individuals and
institutions there is about a fifth
that's held intergovernment so there is
this weird dynamic where you do actually
have different departments of government
owning its own debt on top of that most
of US government debt is held
domestically which makes consequential
if the government were to ever default
on those payments, right? Because that
means lost money for American citizens
and American companies, right? It sounds
great to just wipe out a debt and start
from scratch, but huge consequences
domestically. And in terms of that other
third or quarter of of the debt
outstanding, uh there are other
countries like China and Japan are big
holders. I believe they have nearly a
trillion dollars each or around a
trillion dollars each of US debt. And
yeah, sadly a lot of consequences to
having this guy take it all on, but I
like that one. That was that was a good
uh pallet cleanser for all the other
ones.
>> Don't ever pay a debt that's been sent
to a collection agency. Instead, let me
show you how to make that [__]
completely disappear or at very least
make it a hell of a lot cheaper. But
Devon, I don't want it to negatively
affect my credit. Fun fact, if it's
already in collections, the damage is
done. Your credit is already [__] So,
you might as well thug it out and try to
save yourself some money. First things
first, you need to understand how debt
collectors actually work. Let's say you
owe Chase Bank $2,000, but you don't pay
it for 6 months. They're going to take
your debt and they're going to sell it
to a collection agency for $1,000. That
agency is going to contact you, try to
get you to pay the two grand. If you
don't, they're going to offer you to
settle your debt for 1,500. You don't do
that, they're going to take your debt
again, sell it to another collection
agency for even cheaper, so on and so
forth. The cycle continues. So, the
longer you hold out, the cheaper it's
going to get, and get every agreement in
writing. It does not matter what they
agree upon over the phone. These people
are [__] scumbags. Second, as soon as
this collection agency buys your debt,
it is no longer yours. It is their debt
now. You did not sign any agreement
saying that you would be legally
obligated to pay this collection agency
any [__] money at all until you
verify who you are. You ever been called
by a collection agency a million [__]
times and all they try to do is get you
to say your name? They won't tell you
who they are, where they're from, why
they're calling you. The reason for that
is because as soon as you say your full
name, and assume that that debt is
actually yours, you've now just given
them a verbal signature or a verbal
agreement that you're going to pay them
that debt. Not to mention that some
debts have a statute of limitations,
meaning that after a certain amount of
time, they can't come after you in court
and force you to pay that debt or sue
you if you don't pay it. But in some
situations when you say your name and
assume that debt, that timer resets to
zero. But let's say you already told
them your name, you messed up. You
already assumed the debt. What you're
going to do now is request a debt
validation. A debt validation is a list
of documents that they have to legally
provide and have on file that have all
your legal information correct, all your
debt history correct, and all documents
preceding your debt history. And if
they're missing or have any of that
information incorrect, I'm talking
having your birthday off by one day,
you're going to dispute it, and they're
going to have to send you a letter
saying that this debt is now invalid.
Then you're going to take that letter,
send it to the credit bureau, and
they're going to remove it and make it
like it never even existed to begin
with. You're welcome, and you better
[__] follow me.
>> Uh,
okay. Um, I'll be honest. I don't know
if that verifying identity thing is is
real or not, whether that resets your
your statute of limitations timer,
whatever. Uh but to be clear, uh even if
a debt collector has been has paid for
your debt, which is a real thing that
happens, that doesn't mean you are now
legally not obligated to pay that
person, you still are in debt to that
entity, right? Doesn't matter that it's
changed hands. And a debt collector can
still take you to court or petition for
you to be declared bankrupt if this
happens. I I don't think that would
happen with a a small fee like $2,000,
uh given that the legal fees and the
like would likely not make it worth it.
But you still have that that exposure,
that liability in your name. And I
wouldn't bank on a typo to to get you
out of it. And if courts do intervene,
they have tools like garnishing your
wages, for example. So any money you
earned uh gets directly transferred,
some portion of it to your creditor. So
you can't just ignore your debts and
assume that, you know, it'll be forgiven
if you if you thug it out as as stated
here. Especially because the whole time
that this is outstanding, that means you
can't get a mortgage on a new home. You
can't get credit card debt. uh and as
long as this is outstanding, you haven't
started healing your credit score so
that you can then use debt in the
future. So even if you aren't taken to
court, even if this does eventually get
forgiven, that's a lot. That's a big
cost you've taken and a long period of
time that you've gone restricting
yourself from that sort of financial
access. Whenever you're in a situation
like this, don't take TikTok advice uh
because it might have unintended
consequences that aren't covered in this
video. Definitely reach out to a
professional. In the US, there are
certified credit counselors. In Canada,
we have licensed insolveny trustees.
They can advise you on your options,
including things like declaring
bankruptcy, which have a lot of personal
protections in place or a consumer
proposal where you negotiate for a
better payment plan. But importantly,
when you take these types of actions of,
you know, refusing to take phone calls
or refusing to negotiate, that actually
reduces your likelihood of getting a
favorable ruling or treatment by the
courts. So, don't take advice from
TikTok. A lot of risk of of unintended
consequences with these approaches.
Definitely speak to a professional if
you find yourself in this type of
situation.
>> Is day trading gambling? Overall, the
answer is yes.
>> A lot of day trading ones today. I don't
know why. That's just what just what was
found.
>> But the best way I could describe it is
gambling, but the odds are in your
favor. When you enter a trade, it either
goes up or down 50/50, which is
basically a coin flip. But
hypothetically, if you could guess that
coin flip and make $1,000, and you
watched that person flip the coin for
three years straight, where they placed
it on their thumb, how hard they were
flipping it, what it looked like in the
air, do you think after 3 years of
watching every single thing happen and
journaling all of it, do you think you
could guess it more than 50/50? If you
do think you could, that's what trading
is right there.
Come on. Big money. Big money.
Damn. Absolutely devastating. Well,
everyone, that was the 10th investment
analyst reacts to investing Tik Toks. I
hope you found it helpful. Hope we
learned a little bit of something. If
you liked it, please make sure to like,
subscribe, all that good stuff. It does
help the channel tremendously. Let me
know your thoughts on your favorite Tik
Tok, your favorite uh tips and wisdom
that we garnered here today, and any
other uh content you'd like me to react
to. If there's a movie or uh piece of
media that you'd like to have my input
on, uh then let me know down below, and
I'll do my best to to get to the popular
ideas. Uh, but thank you again for
joining me once again.